

SHOON LEI PHYU (REI)

Saitama, Japan 🔒

+818091834964

shoonleiphyu97@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/reislp/ in





OBJECTIVE

Proactive youth innovator who is studying Digital Business and Innovation (Master) at Tokyo International University. I excel the skills of managing IT projects, providing digital solutions, website development and IT consulting acquired from the knowledge of working 3 years in the insurance industry and B2B IT consulting industry. I am currently looking for the AI Engineer/Product Development positions where I can utilize the website development skills, Python skill, Product Development concepts and project management skills.



EXPERIENCE

Al Engineer - Part-Time

Araya Inc., I Tokyo, JP

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

- Development of Computer Vision Models using Web Camera, Surveillance Cameras and Meeting Platforms using Python, JavaScript and Al Models
- Development of the chrome extension that is supportive to the current AI models.

DIGITAL SOLUTION EXECUTIVE

PRUDENTIAL MYANMAR LIFE INSURANCE CO. LTD., I Yangon, MM

JUNE 2020 - APRIL 2022

Tasks

- Managed the implementation and go-live of digital insurance products (PRUHealth and PRUShoppe) across channels; website and mobile
- Draw the user journeys as required and brainstormed the user experience with C-levels using Figma
- Acted as the product owner of developing features in the Pulse AI application, managing error tickets, finding solutions using Agile method and JIRA
- Coordinated in the implementation of Digital Payments & Partnerships and able to collaborate with the local big companies: KBZ pay, MPT pay, CB pay, OK dollar, 2C2P, and able to open the digital payments using cards, wallet and direct digital web payment for buying the insurance products via Pulse App
- Revise the SLAs, PLAs and Legal Contracts for Partnerships, Influencer Marketing and FinTech Partnerships together with Legal Department
- Generated 5 million digital sales during the Prudential 7 days hot house period via Pulse
- Monitored any product change request and assist when required in resolving production related problems with SRA and Business Requirements, and managed the test cases in testing period across departments

Awards

- The Star Performer Award for the excellence in performance, communication and team accomplishments
- Exceptional Effort Award in Pulse Al application given by CEO.

IT ASSOCIATE

FORVAL MYANMAR CO.LTD., I Yangon, MM

APRIL 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

 Delivered ERP web applications for the B2B and B2C customers within specific timeframes using KINTONE platform and JavaScript, RESTful APIs. (Industries: telecommunication, agriculture, automobile and HR.)



EDUCATION

M.SC IN DIGITAL BUSINESS AND INNOVATION

TOKYO INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY I TOKYO, JAPAN

APRIL 2022 - PRESENT

Coursework: Entrepreneurship Strategy, Python Programming for Data Analysis, Al Product Development, Innovation Management, Implementation of Blockchain Technology with a project, New Product Development **Thesis**: Legal document summarization (in Progress)

Publication: Solving the business owner's solutions and suggesting jobs for young people by using topic modelling and recommendation system (In Progress)

Awards: Recipient of Monbukagakusho Scholarship for International Students

LLM (COMMERCIAL LAWS)

UNIVERSITY OF YANGON I YANGON, MYANMAR

JANUARY 2019 - MARCH 2022

GPA: 4.5

Laws: Commercial Laws, Intellectual Property Laws, Taxation, Foreign Investments

Thesis: Legal Protection of Utility Model in Japan and Myanmar 2021

Activities: Best Basketball Player (Center Position) in 2022, participated as Myanmar representative in JENESYS Cultural Exchange program, selected as finalist in business model proposal competition.

B.SC (Hons) BUSINESS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY OF GREENWICH I LONDON, UNITED KINGDOM

JUNE 2013 - FEBUARY 2017

Second Upper Degree

Coursework: Website Design and Development, Networking and IT Infra Security

Project: POS System of Ngwe Wathone Co. Ltd.,



SKILLS

- Technical: Python, PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Website Design, UIUX
- Tools: GitHub, Figma, JIRA, Confluence, Google Suite, SVN
- Language: Burmese (Native), English (fluent), Japanese (Conversational)